http://phc-online.com/terms_privacy.asp

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site,
place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or
communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.When
ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address,
mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other
information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.We
also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill
the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is
not used for marketing purposes.Like many websites, we use
"cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about
visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use
'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use
them.How do we use your information?We
may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase
products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or
marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site
features in the following ways:To personalize your site
experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product
offerings in which you are most interested.To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.To quickly process your transactions.To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.If
you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you
periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional
e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or
modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have
not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these
e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features
such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a
choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive
e-mail communications from us.How do we protect visitor information?We
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information. Your personal information is contained behind
secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons
who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to
keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your
personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All
sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure
Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to
be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes.
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)
that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your
browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we
use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping
cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based
on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you
with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile
aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can
offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may
contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better
understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not
permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help
us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your
computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose
to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like
Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a
little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the
correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't
have access to many features that make your site experience more
efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However,
you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer
service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance
notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not
include www.phc-online.com. It also does not include website hosting
partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website,
conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties
agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your
information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the
law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights,
property, or safety.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To
modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your
preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email
production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To
delete all of your online account information from our database, sign
into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping
addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note
that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction
in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn
an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third
party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or
liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome
any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link
does not work).Questions and feedbackWe
welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please
send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
